Guide to the Collins Land Company (Helena, Mont.) Records 1898-1951
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
Collins Land Company Records
1898-1951
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections The University of Montana—Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
Mss 063
Collins Land Company (Helena, Mont.)
45.5 linear feet 81 archival boxes and 3 oversize volumes
This collection contains correspondence, financial, legal, promotional, and organizational records generated by the Collins Land Company as well as government publications regarding federal public lands and business records from three other Collins family enterprises. The Collins Land Company was based in Helena, Montana, and bought and sold public lands.
Historical Note
Jeremiah Collins was born in Ireland in 1850 and came to America as a child. Orphaned at age twelve, he worked his way through public schools and Indiana State University in Terre Haute, from which he graduated in 1873. He went into journalism, working first for the Wabash News, then the Logansport Courier. He married Letta E. Fitzgerald in 1878; together, they went to Fort Benton, Montana Territory. In Fort Benton, he established the River Press, which he edited until 1887. He also established the Great Falls Tribune in 1885. In 1889, he withdrew from newspapering to write a history of Montana. After completing that project, he was appointed receiver of public money in the United States General Land Office.
In 1889, Collins established the Collins Land Company in Helena, Montana. The company dealt with public lands, and bought and sold land scrip and represented clients to the Department of the Interior with regard to public lands. This company was so successful that he opened an eastern branch office in Washington, DC, in 1901. The Collins Land Company was one of the largest land scrip dealers in the United States and continued in the business until 1957, when Congress discontinued the use of scrip.
Collins had two children: Lena Agnes and Ted E. He died in 1934 in Washington.
Ted E. Collins took over the Land Company after his father's death and operated it until his death in 1956. The company had expanded into the insurance business in 1910, and that portion of the business increased steadily as the land scrip business declined.
Margaret Chivers was president of the company when its corporate charter expired in 1974 and it ceased to conduct business.
The Collins Realty Company was incorporated in Helena in 1909. Its charter expired in 1929. The Collins Company was incorporated in 1906, and its charter expired in 1926. The Beartooth Stock Company was a livestock raising and agricultural development business headquartered in Helena, Montana.
This collection contains correspondence, financial, legal, promotional, and organizational records generated by the Collins Land Company as well as government publications regarding federal public lands and business records from three other Collins family enterprises. The Collins Land Company was based in Helena, Montana, and bought and sold public lands. Materials in this collection provide particular insights into the history, procedures, and economy of public land management and sale during the first half of the twentieth century.
The collection is divided into eight series:
Series I: Correspondence, 12.5 linear feet, 1898-1938
Subseries 1: General Correspondence, 7 folders, 1898-1938
Subseries 2: Incoming Correspondence, 5.25 linear feet, 1900-1909
Subseries 3: Outgoing Correspondence, 6.25 linear feet, 1898-1909
Subseries 4: Interoffice Correspondence, 1.0 linear feet, 1901-1936
Series II: Case Files, 28.5 linear feet, 1907-1951
Subseries 1: Sequence 1, 7.5 linear feet
Subseries 2: Sequence 2, 9.0 linear feet
Subseries 3: Sequence 3, 11.5 linar feet
Subseries 4: Sequence 4, 0.5 linear feet
Series III: Legal and Financial, 1.5 linear feet adn 2 oversize volumes, 1900-1921
Series IV: Printed Materials, 1.0 linear foot, 1899-1951
Series V: Organization, 0.25 linear feet, 1899-1919
Series VI: Collins Realty Company, 0.5 linear feet, and 1 oversize volume, 1909-1920
Series VII: Collins Company, 0.25 linear feet, 1906-1920
Series VIII: Beartooth Stock Company, 0.25 linear feet, 1912-1939
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and The University of Montana--Missoula.
The materials were largely in the possession of the Collins Land Company until time of donation.
Gift of Margaret Chivers, 1974; gift of Gary Williams, 1979; transferred from the Montana Historical Society, 1979.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Beartooth Stock Company; Collins Company (Helena, Mont.); Collins Realty Company
Homestead law--United States; Land companies--Montana--Helena; Public land sales--United States; Public lands--United States; Real estate business--Montana--Helena
Business records--Montana--Helena
Montana; Labor History; Helena
- Correspondence, 1898-1938; Series I; 12.5 linear feet
  This series contains incoming, outgoing, interoffice and general correspondence generated and collected by the Collins Land Company detailing business projects, proposals, and practices spanning the first four decades of company operation. Series materials are almost exclusively exchanges with clients, potential buyers, and Federal land management officials. These records provide insights into the procedures and economy of public land sales during the first half of the 20th Century.
  - General Correspondence, 1898-1938; Subseries 1; 7 folders
    - General definition of script, 1929 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Alabama Rights, 1906 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Forest Reserve Scrip, 1898-1907 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Gerard Scrip, undated (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Settler's Rights Scrip, 1917 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Explanation of Soldier's Additional Scrip, 1899-1917 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - 1910-1938 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1900-1909; Subseries 2; 5.25 linear feet
    - 1900-1901 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - A, 1902 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - B, 1902 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - C, 1902 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - C, 1902 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - D, 1902 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - E, 1902 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - F, 1902 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - G, 1902 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - H, 1902 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - I, 1902 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - J, 1902 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - K, 1902 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - L, 1902 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - M, 1902 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - N, 1902 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - N, 1902 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - O, 1902 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - P, 1902 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Q, 1902 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - R, 1902 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - R, 1902 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - S, 1902 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - T, 1902 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - United States, 1902 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - United States, 1902 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - United States, 1902 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - United States, 1902 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - U, 1902 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - V, 1902 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - W, 1902 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Y, 1902 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - A, 1903 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - B, 1903 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - C, 1903 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - D, 1903 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - E, 1903 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - F, 1903 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - G, 1903 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - H, 1903 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - I, 1903 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - J, 1903 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - K, 1903 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - L, 1903 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - M, 1903 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - N, 1903 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - O, 1903 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - P, 1903 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - R, 1903 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - S, 1903 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - T, 1903 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - United States, 1903 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - United States, 1903 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - United States, 1903 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - United States, 1903 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - United States, 1903 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - United States, 1903 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - U-V, 1903 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - W, 1903 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - X-Z, 1903 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - A, 1904 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - B, 1904 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - C, 1904 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - C, 1904 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - D, 1904 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - E, 1904 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - F, 1904 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - F, 1904 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - G, 1904 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - H, 1904 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - H, 1904 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - I-J, 1904 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - K, 1904 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - L, 1904 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - M, 1904 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - M, 1904 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - N, 1904 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - O, 1904 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - P, 1904 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Q-R, 1904 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - S, 1904 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - S, 1904 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - T, 1904 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - United States, 1904 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - United States, 1904 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - U-V, 1904 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - W, 1904 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - X-Z, 1904 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - A, 1905 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - B, 1905 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - C, 1905 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - C, 1905 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - D, 1905 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - E, 1905 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - F, 1905 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - G, 1905 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - H, 1905 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - H, 1905 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - I-J, 1905 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - K, 1905 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - L, 1905 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - M, 1905 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - N-O, 1905 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - P, 1905 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Q-R, 1905 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - S, 1905 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - T, 1905 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - U-V, 1905 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - W, 1905 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Y, 1905 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - 1906 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - 1909 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1898-1909; Subseries 3; 6.25 linear feet
    - Letterpress, November 1898-June 1899 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Letterpress, November 1899-June 1900 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Letterpress, August-December 1901 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Letterpress, December 1901-April 1902 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Letterpress, April-July 1902 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Letterpress, July 1902-March 1903 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Letterpress, March-August 1903 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Letterpress, August 1903-April 1904 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Letterpress, April-July 1904 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Letterpress, July-October 1904 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Letterpress, October 1904-February 1905 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Letterpress, February-May 1905 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Letterpress, May-July 1905 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Letterpress, July-October 1905 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Letterpress, October 1905-February 1906 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Letterpress, February-June 1906 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Letterpress, June-September 1906 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Letterpress, September 1906-April 1907 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Letterpress, April-August 1907 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Letterpress, August-December 1907 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Letterpress, December 1907-June 1908 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Letterpress, June-October 1908 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Letterpress, October 1908-April 1909 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Letterpress, April-May 1909 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Letterpress, June 1907-March 1908 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Washington Office, March 1908-May 1909 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Ranches, January 1905-November 1906 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Ranches, February 1906-April 1909 (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Interoffice Correspondence, 1901-1936; Subseries 4; 1.0 linear feet
    - 1901 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - January-November 1902 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - December 1902 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - January-February 1903 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - March-April 1903 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - May-June 1903 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - July-August 1903 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - January-May 1904 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - June-August 1904 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - September-December 1904 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - January-February 1905 (Box-folder 24/4)
    - March-April 1905 (Box-folder 24/5)
    - May-December 1905 (Box-folder 24/6)
    - 1908-1936 (Box-folder 24/7)
- Case Files, 1907-1951; Series II; 28.5 linear feet
  This series contains land scrip case histories collected by the Collins Land Company as documentation for title purchases and transfers. The Collins Land Company created four distinct sequences for these case histories and attached a case number to each file (beginning at zero for each sequence). The original sequences and case numbers have been retained for historical reference; however, records explaining the tracking system rationale and detailing gaps in each sequence no longer existed at the time the collection was accessioned to the archives. These records provide early property definitions and ownership histories for land parcels across the United States, with particular emphasis on Montana and the Pacific Northwest.
  - Sequence 1, Subseries 1; 7.5 linear feet
    - Wright, Mark W., Valley Town, Montana, Case Number 1 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Duer, Charles and Herman, Stanford, Montana, Case Number 2 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - John H. Page and Company, Phoenix, Arizona, Case Number 39 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Shannon, John H., Lewis, Montana, Case Number 40 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Simpson, William L., Cody, Wyoming, Case Number 41 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Elliot, Alexander, Malta, Montana, Case Number 42 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Northern Pacific Scrip, Case Number 54 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Quigley, John R., Avon, Montana, Case Number 62 (Box-folder 25/8)
    - Crowell, Walter and J., Dell, Montana, Case Number 63 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Holliday, Stanford M., Delpine, Montana, Case Number 64 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - W. E. Moses Land Scrip and Realty Company Denver, Colorado, Case Number 65 (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Davenport, Don, Calexico, California, Case Number 66 (Box-folder 25/12)
    - Burke, John H., Helena, Montana, Case Number 67 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - Wheeler, Marion P., Casper, Wyoming, Case Number 68 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - Christianson, Matt, Fishtrap, Montana, Case Number 69 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - Pump, Henry, Martinsdale, Montana, Case Number 70 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Blankenbaker, Virgil F., Virgelle, Montana, Case Number 71 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - Cowan and Son, Box Elder, Montana, Case Number 72 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Herrin, H. J., Wolf Creek, Montana, Case Number 73 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - G. W. Hume Company, Seattle, Washington, Case Number 74 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Clark and Wolcott Buffalo, Wyoming, Case Number 75 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Comyns, E. M., Seattle, Washington, Case Number 76 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - Sprinkle, James L., Chinook, Montana, Case Number 77 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - McIntosh, William L., Avon, Montana, Case Number 78 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - Barth, A. H., Billings, Montana, Case Number 79 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - Trenam, A. L., Weiser, Idaho, Case Number 80 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - Osnes, Ole G., Square Butte, Montana, Case Number 81 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Hedrick, J. G., Halley, Idaho, Case Number 82 (Box-folder 26/11)
    - Paul, Bert H. and Guerry, Homer, Monida, Montana, Case Number 83 (Box-folder 26/12)
    - Holliday, Stanford M., Delpine, Montana, Case Number 84 (Box-folder 26/13)
    - Barker-Wilson Company, Butte, Montana, Case Number 86 (Box-folder 26/14)
    - McIntosh, William L., Avon, Montana, Case Number 89 (Box-folder 26/15)
    - Hazelbaker, Frank A., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 90 (Box-folder 26/16)
    - Frary and Burlingame, Great Falls, Montana, Case Number 91 (Box-folder 26/17)
    - Rhodes, W. E., Glasgow, Montana, Case Number 92 (Box-folder 26/18)
    - Hazelbaker, Frank A., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 93 (Box-folder 26/19)
    - Duff and Duff, Chinook, Montana, Case Number 94 (Box-folder 26/20)
    - Nutting, L. A., Laurel, Montana, Case Number 95 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Gunnison and Robertson, Juneau, Alaska, Case Number 96 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Phillips, B. D., Phillips, Montana, Case Number 97 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Spaulding, P. W., Evanston, Wyoming, Case Number 98 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Granite-BiMetallic Company, Philipsburg, Montana, Case Number 99 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Austin, Charles H., Cascade, Montana, Case Number 100 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Cavene, C. M., Chicago, Illinois, Case Number 102 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Brook-Nook Stock Ranche Company, South Bellingham, Washington, Case Number 103 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - Patterson, Charles F., Pinedale, Wyoming, Case Number 104 (Box-folder 27/9)
    - Pigott, Harry H., Helena, Montana, Case Number 106 (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Miracle, Frank D., Helena, Montana, Case Number 107 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - McIntosh, William L., Avon, Montana, Case Number 108 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Gunnison and Robertson, Juneau, Alaska, Case Number 109 (Box-folder 27/13)
    - Henry, Charles F., Townsend, Montana, Case Number 110 (Box-folder 27/14)
    - Cheney, A. V., Stanford, Montana, Case Number 111 (Box-folder 27/15)
    - Ness, Casper, Two Dot, Montana, Case Number 112 (Box-folder 27/16)
    - Moulton, C. E., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 113 (Box-folder 27/17)
    - Crossen, Hays W., Harlem, Montana, Case Number 114 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Boone, R. W., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 115 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Blankenbaker, Virgil F., Virgelle, Montana, Case Number 132 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Lander State Bank Lander, Wyoming, Case Number 135 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Elliot, Thomas, St. Anthony, Idaho, Case Number 143 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Lannen, Chris, Bearmouth, Montana, Case Number 145 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Flowerree Sheep and Horse Company, Lowry, Montana, Case Number 152 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Wagner, Peter, West Butte, Montana, Case Number 154 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Brimmer and Brimmer, Rawlins, Wyoming, Case Number 155 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Merchants Loan Company, Billings, Montana, Case Number 156 (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Barley Selection Right, Case Number 157 (Box-folder 28/11)
    - Eastern Idaho Loan and Trust Company, Idaho Falls, Idaho, Case Number 158 (Box-folder 28/12)
    - Beartooth Stock Company, Helena, Montana, Case Number 161 (Box-folder 28/13)
    - Wagner, Peter, West Butte, Montana, Case Number 165 (Box-folder 28/14)
    - Higby, Guy W., Lander, Wyoming, Case Number 166 (Box-folder 28/15)
    - Brearley and Williams, Alder, Montana, Case Number 167 (Box-folder 28/16)
    - Boone, R. W., Dillon, Montana, Case Number 172 (Box-folder 28/17)
    - Dickie, David, Dickie, Wyoming, Case Number 179 (Box-folder 28/18)
    - Wick, O. T., Duluth, Minnesota, Case Number 181 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Brimmer and Brimmer, Rawlins, Wyoming, Case Number 185 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - Shaw, A. C., Portland, Oregon, Case Number 197 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Chabot, Virgil, Big Trails, Wyoming, Case Number 505 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Marshall, Charles, Sitka, Alaska, Case Number 731 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Hubbell and Waller Engineering Corporation, Seattle, Washington, Case Number 931A (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Hubbell and Waller Engineering Corporation, Seattle, Washington, Case Number 931 (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Liberty Montana Mining Company, Jefferson Island, Montana, Case Number 932A (Box-folder 29/8)
    - Liberty Montana Mining Company, Jefferson Island, Montana, Case Number 932 (Box-folder 29/9)
    - Liberty Montana Mining Company, Jefferson Island, Montana, Case Number 932B (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Witter, C. B., Helena, Montana, Case Number 967 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Olsen, DeForrest A., Case Number 1226 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Mason, Nelson A., Bismarck, North Dakota, Case Number 1272 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - McKee Scrip, Case Number 1323 (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Johnson, George L., Anchorage, Alaska, Case Number 1345 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - City of Shelby, Montana, Case Number 1404 (Box-folder 30/7)
    - Freeman, Mrs. Margaret, Case Number 1419 (Box-folder 30/8)
    - Kuhr, W. H., Chinook, Montana, Case Number 1433 (Box-folder 30/9)
    - Waldron, Miss M. B., Anchorage, Alaska, Case Number 1453 (Box-folder 30/10)
    - Lockey, Richard, Palo Alto, California, Case Number 1456 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Murphy, Thomas J., Kitscoty, Alberta, Case Number 1529 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Haines, Mary E., Narrows, Oregon, Case Number 1659 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Heirs of Bertie N. Durbin, Case Number 1700 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Hodell, Anna, Sheridan, Wyoming, Case Number 1704 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Calkins, Joel P., Leigh, Nebraska, Case Number 1705 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - Haydon, Isabella, Case Number 1710 (Box-folder 31/7)
    - Cushenberry, John, Shoshoni, Nebraska, Case Number 1711 (Box-folder 31/8)
    - Inghram, Ted, Moeta, Wyoming, Case Number 1714 (Box-folder 31/9)
    - Pratt, Henry A., Conway, Kansas, Case Number 1721 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - Lambert, Della, Case Number 1725 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Harrington, Minnie C., Siloam Springs, Arkansas, Case Number 1727 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Heirs of Archie Edgerly, Upper Mattole, California, Case Number 1729 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Heirs of Fred Bragg, Upper Mattole, California, Case Number 1732 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Kirkland, William J., Case Number 1735 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Walker, Myrtle S., Traverse City, Michigan, Case Number 1737 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Odell, George W., Chicago, Illinois, Case Number 1742 (Box-folder 32/7)
    - Wills, Saladin H., Chicago, Illinois, Case Number 1747 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Sanders, William J., Chicago, Illinois, Case Number 1752 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Messenger, Jacob, Bakersfield, California, Case Number 1753 (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Griffin, Charles O., Jr., Sundance, Wyoming, Case Number 1755 (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Craig, Byron H., Sundance, Wyoming, Case Number 1762 (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Englar, Francis M., Sundance, Wyoming, Case Number 1773 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Vis, John J., Alameda, California, Case Number 1774 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Williams, Mary H., Alameda, California, Case Number 1782 (Box-folder 32/15)
    - New, Nathan N., Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1786 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Till, James O., Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1788 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Leonard, George E., Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1794 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Gurley, Stephen A. D., Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1795 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Ross, Oscar T., Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1797 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Chase, Harvey J., Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1798 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - Scofield, Jesse E., Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1799 (Box-folder 33/7)
    - Sperr, Christian J., Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1801 (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Barnes, William, Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1804 (Box-folder 33/9)
    - Anderson, Josephine, Plain Dealing, Louisiana, Case Number 1805 (Box-folder 33/10)
    - Green, Fred A., Seattle, Washington, Case Number 1806 (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Shaddy, Mahmond, Seattle, Washington, Case Number 1808 (Box-folder 33/12)
    - Henderson, May, Seattle, Washington, Case Number 1810 (Box-folder 33/13)
    - Ruechel, Adolph J., Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 1811 (Box-folder 33/14)
    - Gould, Frank S., Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 1813 (Box-folder 33/15)
    - White, Ranson, Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 1815 (Box-folder 33/16)
    - Hanesalo, Eruk (deceased), Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 1816 (Box-folder 34/1)
    - McClean, William S., Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 1819 (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Serna, Liben, Kalispell, Montana, Case Number 1820 (Box-folder 34/3)
    - Miller, John B., Oakland, California, Case Number 1822 (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Douster, Jacob, Oakland, California, Case Number 1823 (Box-folder 34/5)